Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual and graphics records, circa 1869-2014; 1950-1984; Series 1; 24 Linear Feet
  - Photographs, circa 1890-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Over 1,353 images
    - CSA: Publications reproductions of letters and articles about the school used for display, 1975; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - CSA: Faculty Jessalee Sickman (matted), undated; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Slides, circa 1965-1984; Series 1 subseries 2
    Contains color slides of Gallery activities, collections, student projects,and exhibitions.
    - 27th Biennial rejects, 1961; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 1, Segment 1)
    - 28th Biennial, 1963; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 1, Segment 2)
    - 29th Biennial, 1965; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 1, Segment 3)
    - 30th Biennial, 1967; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 1, Segment 4)
    - Richard Woodville, 1967 April 21-June 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 1, Segment 5)
    - Light and Art, 1967 October 23-1968 May 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 1, Segment 6)
    - Adolph Gottlieb, 1968 April 26-June 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 1)
    - Hairy Who?, 1969 April; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 2)
    - Thomas Eakins, 1969 May 2-June 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 3)
    - Vincent Melzac Collection, 1971; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 4)
    - 32nd Biennial - David Novros, 1971 February 28-April 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 5)
    - 32nd Biennial - Richard Jackson, 1971 February 28-April 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 6)
    - 32nd Biennial, 1971 February 28-April 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 7)
    - Sonia Delauney Tapestries, 1972 October 20-November 26; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 8)
    - Lowell Nesbit, 1973 April 13-May 27; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 9)
    - Eric Rudd, 1973 April 13-May 27; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 10)
    - Thomas Wilfred, 1973 April 17-May 30; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 11)
    - Michael Tyzack, 1973 June 1-30; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 12)
    - Leon Berkowitz, 1973 September 14-October 14; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 2, Segment 13)
    - 34th Biennial, 1977 September 26-April 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 3, Segment 1)
    - Helen Frankenthaler, 1975 April 19-June 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 4, Segment 2)
    - 35th Biennial, 1977 February 26-April 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 4, Segment 3)
    - 35th Biennial [end], 1977 February 26-April 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 4, Segment 4)
    - Paul Outerbridge, 1977 April 20-May 29; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 4, Segment 5)
    - Norman Bluhm, 1977 June 4-July 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 1)
    - Howard Mehring, 1977 December 10-1978 January 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 2)
    - 36th Biennial, 1979 February 24-April 8; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 3)
    - Gene Davis, 1978 December 16-1979 February 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 4)
    - BFA - Rowe, 1982 January 15-March 28; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 5)
    - BFA - Thomas, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 6)
    - BFA - Tolliver, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 7)
    - BFA - Traylor, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 8)
    - BFA - White, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 5, Segment 9)
    - New World: Masterpieces of American Painting, 1983 December 7-1984 February 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 6, Segment 1)
    - Indelible Image - slides for exhibition catalog books, 1986 April 26-June 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 6, Segment 2)
    - Indelible Image - David Culverwell (potential lender), 1986 April 26-June 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 6, Segment 3)
    - Indelible Image - Bill Hackwell (potential lender), 1986 April 26-June 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 6, Segment 4)
    - Indelible Image - Chris Phillips (researcher), 1986 April 26-June 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 29, Box 6, Segment 5)
    - BFA - George Williams, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 7, Segment 1)
    - BFA - Luster Willis, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 7, Segment 2)
    - BFA - Joseph Yoakum, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 7, Segment 3)
    - BFA - unidentified slides, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 7, Segment 4)
    - Northern Light, 1982 September 11-October 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 7, Segment 5)
    - 38th Biennial, 1983 February 3-April 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 7, Segment 6)
    - Niagara, 1985 September 21-November 24; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 1)
    - Surrogate Selves, Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 2)
    - 41st Biennial, 1989 April 5-June 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 3)
    - John Torreano - Gallery One, 1989 May 11-July 30; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 4)
    - Facing History, 1990 January 13-March 25; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 5)
    - Deserts of the South West, 1990 May 19-August 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 6)
    - Terra Sancta - Peter von zur Muehlen, 1990 May 19-August 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 7)
    - Terra Sancta - Bernis von zur Muehlen, 1990 May 19-August 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 8)
    - Terra Sancta - Arnold Kramer, 1990 May 19-August 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 9)
    - Reckoning with Winslow Homer, 1991 March 16-June 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 10)
    - Max Weber, the Cubist Decade, 1992 May 30-August 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 11)
    - Keith Haring, Andy Warhol, Walt Disney, 1992 June 6-August 23; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 8, Segment 12)
    - 43rd Biennial, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 1)
    - Meeting History, 1994 January 29-April 10; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 2)
    - Luxor v1.0, 1994 September 17-November 7; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 3)
    - Louis Bourgeois: The Locus of Memory, 1994 September 24-1995 January 8; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 4)
    - Pedro Meyer, 1995 March 11-May 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 5)
    - Niek Kemps, 1995 September 23-December 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 6)
    - Artsites 96, 1996 May 29-July 29; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 7)
    - Picturing History, 1994 January 29; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 8)
    - David Mordini Heads, 1996 September 1-November 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 9)
    - Faberge and Finland, 1996 October 16-1997 January 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 10)
    - Jewels of the Romonovs, 1997 January 29-1997 April 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 11)
    - Mark Bennett: TV sets, 1997 May 17-August 10; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 12-17)
    - New Worlds from Old, 1999 January 27-April 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 30, Box 9, Segment 18-19, Box 10)
    - Works of Art, A-L, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 11)
    - Works of Art, M-Z, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 30, Box 12)
    - ODYSSEY: The Art of Photography at National Geographic, 1988 June 4-August 28; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 31, Box 13-16)
    - ODYSSEY: The Art of Photography at National Geographic, 1988 June 4-August 28; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 31, Box 17, Segment 1)
    - Children's Program workshops, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 31, Box 17, Segment 2)
    - Vincent Melzac Collection, circa 1970; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 31, Box 17, Segment 3, Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art I and II: Exterior Views (slides), undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Permanent Collection, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Selections from the Permanent Collection: Contemporary Art, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Bosnia-Gilles Peress, 1994 March 5-May 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Alfred Stieglitz, 1995 May 6-July 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - American Politicians, 1995 July 14-September 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Pedro Meyer, 1995 March 11-May 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Runaways: Slides and Negatives, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Runaways: Prints, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Richard Bolton, 1995 December 6-1996 January 14; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Godfrey Frankel, 1996 December 16-February 19; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Hospice, 1996 March 9-May 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Recent acquisitions of photography, 1996 March 13-June 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Sonnenstand, 1996 May 11-July 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Photography as a Reflection of Time, 1996 June 12-September 8; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Space, Time, and Memory, 1996 June 15-August 26; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Sigmar Polke, 1996 September 21-December 16; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Temple of Confessions, 1996 October 12-1997 January 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Jewels of the Romanovs, 1997 January 22-April 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Keeping Time, 1997 May 3-June 14; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Gordon Parks, 1997 September 10-1998 January 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Ida Applebroog, 1998 March 14-June 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Rhapsodies in Black, 1998 April 11-June 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Alchemy - Ashton Harris, 1998 May 2-August 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Larrabee - Life in Wartime, 1998 August 15-October 18; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Roy De Carava, 1998 October 17-1999 January 10; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Developing Illusions, 1998 November 14-1999 January 18; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Propaganda and Dreams, 1999 May 13-August 23; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Homelessness, 1999 December 4-2000 January 31; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Arnold Newman, 2000 March 18-May 21; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - 46th Biennial, 2000 December 8-2001 March 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Native Land, 2001 May 12-August 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Arthur Tress, 2001 July 1-September 23; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Kertesz + Fried, 2001 July 21-September 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Nature Conservancy, 2001 September 15-December 31; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Wendy Ewald, 2002 January 19-April 8; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Jasper Johns to Jeff Koons, 2002 March 16-June 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Jacqueline Kennedy, 2002 April 6-September 30; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Tretick - The Kennedy Years, 2002 July 1-November 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Gilded Cage, 2002 July 13-August 27; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Here Is New York, 2002 September 7-November 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Joan Miro, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Emmet Gowin, 2002 October 26-2003 January 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - 47th Biennial, 2002 December 21-2003 March 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Joseph Mills - Inner City, 2003 February 15-April 14; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Both Sides of the Street, 2003 April 12-July 28; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Robert Frank, 2003 May 12-July 14; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - American Paradigms, 2004 February 15-April 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Folk to Funk, 2004 February 21-April 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Muriel Hasbun, 2004 March 6-June 7; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Norman Rockwell, 2004 May 15-September 16; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Anil Revri, 2004 June 5-September 13; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Sally Mann, 2004 June 12-September 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Art + Writing Awards, 2004 June 19-August 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Joan of Arc, 2006 November 18-2007 January 21; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Sight/Insight, 2006 November 1-December 31; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - The Paradise Institute, 2006 October 25-December 31; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Redefined - Modern + Contemporary, 2006 July 15-2007 January 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Robert Weingarten, 2006 July 15-October 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - Scholastic Art + Writing Awards, 2006 July 1-August 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Presidential Scholars, 2006 June 3-25; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Redefined 1 - Modern + Contemporary, 2006 April 4-December 31; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - American Landscape, 2006 April 26-June 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - John Singer Sargent, 2006 February 8-April 19; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Picturing the Banjo, 2005 December 10-2006 March 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Sam Gilliam, 2005 October 15-2006 January 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Warhol, 2005 September 24-2006 February 20; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - William MacLeod, 2005 September 10-November 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Encouraging American Genius, 2005 August 27-2006 January 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Current Evince, 2005 July 2-September 11; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Shomei Tomatsu, 2005 May 21-August 29; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Dutch Silver, 2005 April 29-July 4; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Print Portfolio, 2005 March 26-June 20; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - 48th Corcoran Biennial, 2005 March 19-June 27; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Common Ground, 2004 November 24-2005 January 31; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Inventions - Caio Fonseca, 2004 October 9-2005 February 14; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Frank Gehry Design for Museums, 2004 October 2-2005 March 21; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Furniture of Frank Gehry, 2004 September 22-November 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Andrew Krieger, 2004 July 24-November 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Corcoran Archives collection material images, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folders 21-22)
    - Events, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Exhibitions, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Flagg building interior and exterior, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Renwick Gallery, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Staff, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified duplicates [possibly Mark Bennett], undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - William A. Clark residence, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Works of Art, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1955 July 1-1973 May 27; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1973 June 1-1973 March 3; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1974 February-1975 April 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1975 February 26-April 6; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1975 February 26-1975 September; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1975 September-1976 April; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1976 January-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Exhibition installation slides, 1974-1980; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Events and curatorial department: objects, 1950s-1990s; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 34, Folders 2-6)
    - Exhibit: Mark Bennett, 1985; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Events, 1981 November; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Tokyo String Quartet, undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Exhibit: Northern Lights Opening, 1982 September 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Gurdon Woods: A Retrospective, 1985 September 14-October 19; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 1)
    - Constructed Fictions: Buzz Spector, 1985 October 12-November 2; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 2)
    - Peter Kubelka lecture, 1985 September 27; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 3)
    - Russian Art: A Survey of Contemporary Activities, 1985 October 19-November 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 4)
    - Komar and Melamid lecture, 1985 November 1; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 5)
    - Panel discussion, 1985 November 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 6)
    - 6th Annual Auction, 1985 November 2-15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 1, Segment 7)
    - 6th Annual Auction (con't), 1985 November 2-15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 1)
    - 10 year catalogue preparation, 1985 December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 2)
    - Tom Ashcraft installation, 1985 December 13; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 3)
    - Botswana, 1985 December 13; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 4)
    - Ariane Dubois: Neon Installation, 1985 December 13-1986 January 25; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 5)
    - Trade Show, 1985 December 13-1986 January 25; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 6)
    - Build out Kresge's, 1986; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 7)
    - Alice Denney Fundraiser, 1986; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 8)
    - Party at Yale Laundry Ultra Marine, 1986; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 9)
    - Botswana Polly Schulamn, 1986 January 7-25; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 2, Segment 10)
    - Experimental Theater of the Wooster Group - Elizabeth LeCompte lecture, 1986 January 18; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 1)
    - Kirby Malone: Impossible Theater, 1986 January 18; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 2)
    - Distant Landscapes: John Hull, 1986 February 7-March 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 3)
    - Distant Landscapes: Stephen Estrada, 1986 February 7-March 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 4)
    - Haim Steinbach, 1986 February 7-March 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 5)
    - John Wood, 1986 February 7-March 22; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 6)
    - Paradise to Purgatory, 1986 March 8-April 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 7)
    - Cryptic Language: Henry Chotkowski, 1986 April 7-May 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 8)
    - Cryptic Language: Kay Hines, 1986 April 7-May 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 9)
    - Cryptic Language: Kay Rosen, 1986 April 7-May 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 10)
    - Larry Miller: As if the Universe were an Object, 1986 April 7-May 17; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 11)
    - Mowry Baden, 1986 May 30-July 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 12)
    - Gary Cawood, 1986 May 30-July 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 13)
    - Steve Kruvant, 1986 May 30-July 12; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 14)
    - Dog Dreams Bookworks, 1987; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 15)
    - James L. Wells, 1987; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 3, Segment 16)
    - War and Memory: Terry Allen, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 1)
    - War and Memory: Cynthia Carlson, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 2)
    - War and Memory: Allen Carter, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 3)
    - War and Memory: Nancy Floyd, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 4)
    - War and Memory: Richard Posner, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 5)
    - War and Memory: Joseph Shannon, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 6)
    - War and Memory: Richard Turner, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 7)
    - War and Memory: Wendy Watriss, 1987 September-December; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 8)
    - Life Outside the Law, 1988 January-March; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 9)
    - Jim Hubbard, 1988; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 10)
    - Cut Across, 1988 January 24-March 5; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 11)
    - Exploring the Documentary for Photography/Film - Jim Goldberg, 1988 October-November; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 12)
    - Exploring the Documentary.... - Nathan Lyons, 1988 October-November; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 13)
    - Exploring the Documentary.... - Alan Sekula, 1988 October-November; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 14)
    - Recollections, 1988 December 8-1989 January 21; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 4, Segment 15)
    - Recollections, 1988 December 8-1989 January 21; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 1)
    - Al Souza, 1989; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 2)
    - From the Potomac to the Anacostia, 1989 February 3-April 8; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 3)
    - The Whims of Change: The construction of the Avante Garde, 1989 March-April; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 4)
    - Windsor Installation - Scott Mcarny, 1989 May; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 5)
    - Dream On - Edelson, 1989 May 11-July 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 6)
    - Dream On - Judy Janinsky, 1989 May 11-July 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 7)
    - Dream On - Martin, 1989 May 11-July 15; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 5, Segment 8)
    - Robert Mapplethorpe, 1989 July-August; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 6, Segment 1)
    - The Blues Aesthetic, 1989 September 14-December 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 6, Segment 2)
    - The Blues Aesthetic - Dawoud Bey, 1989 September 14-December 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 6, Segment 3)
    - The Blues Aesthetic - Willie Birch, 1989 September 14-December 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 6, Segment 4)
    - The Blues Aesthetic - Christenberry, 1989 September 14-December 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 6, Segment 5)
    - The Blues Aesthetic - David Hammons, 1989 September 14-December 9; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 57, Box 6, Segment 6)